most
distasteful
self defeat
about Allah
you are really really
deceiving yourself
regarding Allah
when you think that because
of the
wealth
that you enjoy
because of the comfort and
luxury that
you have
that means that Allah
loves you
so irrespective of your deeds
as long as you are luxurious
and comfortable
that means Allah loves you
there are a lot of people
thinking
like this
that when there is money what
is
left
when there is wealth
what is left, we have
everything
I heard
one in a discussion
I read we were having
a discussion with someone who
is
supposed to be learned
this person sees nothing
wrong
in trading
in riba
he was arguing
in an argument he said
something
he said if the
Europeans and the western
world
if they deal in riba
yet we see
them in the opulence that we
have
seen them, then it means
there is nothing wrong with
the riba
this is what Ibn al Qaim said
rahimahullah
wa hadha min aqbahil gurur
billah, this is from the
most distasteful
did Allah not say to us that
do not be deceived
with the
thoughts and backwards of
kufar
in luxury and comfort
in this dunya, don't be
deceived by
it